<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hiring on </title>
    <link>https://buildhello.ca/tags/hiring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hiring on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://buildhello.ca/tags/hiring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build Hello Recruitment</title>
      <link>https://buildhello.ca/newsletter/hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://buildhello.ca/newsletter/hiring/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Build Hello Recruitment We&amp;rsquo;re currently in a start-up stage. That means we&amp;rsquo;re &amp;lsquo;picking teams,&amp;rsquo; so to speak.&#xA;Our Process The process we follow as a start-up, and the process you may want to follow, as a potential Build Hello partner or employee, is similar to the processes professional sports teams follow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starter Package | Build Hello Business | Many fine tasks quickly combined and mixed like pancake batter into one incredibly complete looking website, for just $899?</title>
      <link>https://buildhello.ca/services/starter_package/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://buildhello.ca/services/starter_package/</guid>
      <description>Starting a business means launching a new website, but building it yourself takes forever. Our quickstart starter package delivers the bare minimum. It&amp;rsquo;s an easy way to get something good looking up you can work on later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design | Build Hello Business | Sketches. Scribbles on the back of napkins. Wireframes. Mockups. Prototypes.</title>
      <link>https://buildhello.ca/services/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://buildhello.ca/services/design/</guid>
      <description>Because it feels good to know your website design is original you. We help out with sexy ideas, and even put together prototypes and mockups you can view and share with your team online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Development | Build Hello Business | Basically we build you a space ship, a space station, a space world...whatever you want.</title>
      <link>https://buildhello.ca/services/web_development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://buildhello.ca/services/web_development/</guid>
      <description>When your business is online, customers can see your on their phones! That&amp;rsquo;s where you want to be! Give us a call to help out with, oh any websites you&amp;rsquo;ve ever dreamed of!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Writing | Build Hello Business | Carefully crafted words arranged in clever, campy and carefree, or confident and credible, crisp, non-cursive character strings (assuming you don&#39;t want cursive.)</title>
      <link>https://buildhello.ca/services/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://buildhello.ca/services/content/</guid>
      <description>Text, text, and more text. We write it. We edit it. We make it yours. Content writing for the web is a technical art-form. It&amp;rsquo;s a blend of research, style, and optimization. It&amp;rsquo;s something we do for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refactoring | Build Hello Business | That&#39;s &#39;refactoring of code,&#39; which is to say modernizing and simplifying any...how can we say this politely...&#39;cryptography&#39; you&#39;ve been saddled with into a modern top tier code base.</title>
      <link>https://buildhello.ca/services/refactoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://buildhello.ca/services/refactoring/</guid>
      <description>Refactoring your code base is more than proactive troubleshooting, it&amp;rsquo;s SEO, security, and better functionality all in one. Stay ahead of the crowd, refactor that code base!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maintenance | Build Hello Business | Tracking down that stray semi-colon. Pest Control. Very unpleasant virus removal. Updates!</title>
      <link>https://buildhello.ca/services/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://buildhello.ca/services/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>When you have a website problem, you have a business problem. At Build Hello we put website problems to rest, so your business can rise and shine!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
